A Guide to the John D. Chapla Papers, 1972-2013
Library of Virginia
- Series I. 42nd, 48th, and 50th Virginia Infantry Regiments Research Files., Extent: 34 boxes. (Box 1-29, 47-51)
  - 50th Virginia Infantry Regiment
    - Keith Family Notes. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Robert K. Krick Files. (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
    - Lee County Death Records. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Lee County Pension Applications. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Lee County Sources. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Letters - 50th Virginia Infantry. (Box 24, Folder 10-13)
    - Letters - 50th Virginia Infantry - Vol. 1. (Box 24, Folder 14-17)
    - Letters - 50th Virginia Infantry - Vol. 2. (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
    - Letters - 50th Virginia Infantry - Vol. 3. (Box 25, Folder 5-7)
    - Library of Virginia. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Library of Virginia - R.E. Lee Camp Home Applications. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Maps. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Maps - Bowring Cartographic. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Mayberry/Mabry (Ora Bell Mayberry McColman). (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Militia Records of Lee and Scott Counties. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Mitchell, Thomas F.. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Museum of the Confederacy. (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - National Archives. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - National Archives - Army of the Kanawha Records. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - National Archives - Army of the Potomac Records. (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - National Archives - Inspection Reports. (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Needs Adding to File. (Box 25, Folder 20-22)
    - Noel, Walker Timberlake. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Non-Battle Hospitalizations. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Occupations, Careers/Descriptions, Physical. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Officer Enlistments and Promotions. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Official Records of the War of the Rebellion. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Passages: A History of Amherst County. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Pension Applications. (Box 26, Folder 7-11)
    - Pension Applications - Kentucky. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Perkins Family Notes. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Photographs. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Pre and Post-War Activities. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Pulaski County Sources. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Quesenberry Family Notes. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Record of Events - Compiled Service Records. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Reorganization, 1862. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Reynolds, Alexander W.. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Reynolds, Powell B.. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Roster - 50th Virginia Infantry - First Edition. (Box 47, Folder n/a)
    - Roster - 50th Virginia Infantry - Vol. 1. (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
    - Roster - 50th Virginia Infantry - Vol. 2. (Box 27, Folder 10-11)
    - Roster Numbers - Compiled Service Records. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Roster (Postwar) - Company I - Radford Record, 1922. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Salyer Family Papers. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Scott County History (Robert M. Addington). (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Second Edition. (Box 27, Folder 16-18)
    - Sheffey, John P.. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Smith Family Letters. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Smith Family Letters - Virginia Tech. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Smith, William Adolphus. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Smyth County Families and History (Jim Presgraves). (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Smyth County History (Joan Tracy Armstrong). (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Smyth County Sources. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Robert W. Snead Papers. (Box 28, Folder 8-11)
    - Sources and Numerical Key. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Southern Historical Society Papers. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Stamper - Grayson County Confederate Veterans. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Stuart, William D.. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Summary List of Companies and Roster. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Summers, Lewis Preston - History of Southwest Virginia. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Tazewell County "Annals" (John Newton Harman, Sr.). (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Tazewell County Death Register. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Tazewell County History (William C. Pendleton). (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Tazewell County Roster of Ex-Confederate Soldiers. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Tazewell County Sources. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - U.D.C. Survey for Regimental Histories. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - United States Naval Academy Archives and Museum (C.E. Thorburn). (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Van Deventer Family. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Historical Society. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - "Virginia in the Civil War" Message Board. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Tech. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Wade Family Papers. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Wartime Non-Battle and Postwar Deaths. (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Washington County. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Jeffrey C. Weaver Notes. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Webb-Lewis Family Papers. (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - West, P. Michael. (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - West Virginia University. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Wise County. (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Woosley, Thomas M.. (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Wright Family Notes. (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Wythe County. (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Wythe County, Virginia - A Bicentennial History (Kegley). (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Yates Family Papers. (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Yeatts-Wartell Family. (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Series II. Miscellaneous Subject Files., Extent: 12 boxes. (Box 30-39, 51-52)
  The miscellaneous subject files contain information pertaining to Chapla's interest in Civil War battles and battlefields. There are brochures, guidebooks, and maps from numerous sites mainly in Virginia. This series also includes transcriptions of census records, abstracts and copies of newspaper articles, copies of Virginia disabliity applications from the Library of Virginia, copies of National Archives records and microfilm, maps, and published sources.
  - Alabama Confederate Pensions. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Antietam. (Box 30, Folder 2-4)
  - Appomattox Retreat. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Ashe County, NC. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Bethesda Church. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Book Inventory (Card File). (Box 51, Folder n/a)
  - Boulware and Cox Wharf. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Bristoe Station. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Casualties - ANVA, May-June 1864. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Casualties in Virginia Regiments by Jeff Weaver From Regimental Histories Series. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Cedar Creek. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Cedar Mountain. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Census - 1860. (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Census - 1860 - Notes by Don P. Thomas. (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Census - 1860 - Bedford County. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Census - 1860 - Campbell County. (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Census - 1860 - Carroll County. (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Census - 1860 - Floyd County. (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Census - 1860 - Franklin County. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Census - 1860 - Grayson County. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Census - 1860 - Henry County. (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
  - Census - 1860 - Lee County. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Census - 1860 - Montgomery County. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Census - 1860 - Patrick County. (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
  - Census - 1860 - Pulaski County. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Census - 1860 - Roanoke County. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Census - 1860 - Russell County. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Census - 1860 - Scott County. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Census - 1860 - Smyth County. (Box 32, Folder 2-3)
  - Census - 1860 - Tazewell County. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Census - 1860 - Washington County. (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
  - Census - 1860 - Wise County. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Census - 1890 - Smyth and Washington Counties - Civil War Veterans. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Chancellorsville. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Chancellorsville - Capture of the 21st Virginia Flag. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Chancellorsville - Jones' Brigade Actions, 3 May 1863. (Box 32, Folder 11-12)
  - Chantilly. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Charleston, WV. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Cheat Mountain. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Chickamauga. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Compiled Service Records of Confederate Soldiers Who Served in Organizations From the State of Alabama. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Confederate Army Reorganization, April 1862. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Confederate Veteran. (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
  - Cool Spring. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Cross Keys. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Disablility Applications. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Disablility Applications - Amherst County. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Disablility Applications - Appomattox County. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Disablility Applications - Bedford County. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Disablility Applications - Botetourt County. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Disablility Applications - Bristol. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Disablility Applications - Buchanan County. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Disablility Applications - Campbell County. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Disablility Applications - Carroll County. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Disablility Applications - Craig County. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Disablility Applications - Danville. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Disablility Applications - Floyd County. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Disablility Applications - Franklin County. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Disablility Applications - Giles County. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Disablility Applications - Grayson County. (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Disablility Applications - Henry County. (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Disablility Applications - Idaho. (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Disablility Applications - Lee County. (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Disablility Applications - Lynchburg County. (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Disablility Applications - Montgomery County. (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Disablility Applications - Patrick County. (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Disablility Applications - Pittsylvania County. (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Disablility Applications - Pulaski County. (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Disablility Applications - Roanoke County. (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Disablility Applications - Russell County. (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Disablility Applications - Scott County. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Disablility Applications - Smyth County. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Disablility Applications - Tazewell County. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Disablility Applications - Washington County. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Disablility Applications - Wise County. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Disablility Applications - Wythe County. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Drill and Tactics. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Edinburg, VA. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - "Elyria in the Civil War" by Don Miller. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Fayetteville, WV. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Finns Point National Cemetery (Fort Delaware). (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Fisher's Hill. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Flags - Battle Flags of ANVA. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Flags - Flags of Virginia. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Flags - Hardee's Tactics re: Color Guard. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Flags - Returned Battleflags. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Flash Drive. (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Florida Pension Applications. (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Floyd County - "Sisson's Kingdom" by Paul R. Dotson, Jr. (Thesis). (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Fort Donelson. (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Fort Stedman. (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - 44th Virginia Infantry. (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Fredericksburg. (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Fredericksburg Winter Quarters, 1862-1863. (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Gaines' Mill. (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Gettysburg. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Gettysburg - Flags of Johnson's Division. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Gettysburg - Retreat. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Gordonsville Hospital Death Register. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Guide to Writing - Virginia Regimental Histories Series. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Harper's Ferry. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Hatcher's Run. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Huntersville, Knapp's Creek, Minnehaha Springs. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Huntington Library. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Jones, John R.. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Kernstown. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Lewisburg, WV. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Lynchburg Hospitals. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Lynchburg Undertakers. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Malvern Hill. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Manassas Reenactment, 1961. (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Maps. (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Maps - Louisa County. (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Maps - Orange County. (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - McDowell. (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Medical Terms and Definitions. (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm - Confederate States Army Casualties: Lists and Narrative Reports (M836) - 3 reels. (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Microfilm - 42nd Virginia Infantry Regimental Returns - Pay and Muster Rolls, Clothing Receipts (National Archives). (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Microfilm - 48th Virginia Infantry Returns, Rosters, and Muster Rolls (National Archives). (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Microfilm - General Orders of the Confederate Adjutant and Inspector Generals Office (T782) - Chapter I, Vol. 1, 3-5. (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Microfilm - Irvine-Saunders Papers - UVA. (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Microfilm - Orders and Circulars Issued by the Army of the Potomac and the ANVA (M921) - 4 reels. (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Microfilm - Population Schedules of the Eighth Census of the United States - 1860 - Virginia (Henry, Highland, Isle of Wight, and Jackson Counties). (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Microfilm - Population Schedules of the Eighth Census of the United States - 1860 - Virginia (King and Queen, King William, Lancaster, and Lee Counties). (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Microfilm - Population Schedules of the Eighth Census of the United States - 1860 - Virginia (Russell and Scott Counties). (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Microfilm - Population Schedules of the Eighth Census of the United States - 1860 - Virginia Slave Schedules (Greensville, Halifax, Hampshire, Hanover, Harrison, Henry, Highland, Isle of Wight, and Jackson Counties). (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Missouri Confederate Home Applications. (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Monocacy. (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Museum of the Confederacy - Dabney Award, 2007. (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Musick, Michael P. - "The Little Regiment". (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - National Archives - Amnesty Oaths and Pardons. (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - National Archives - Guide to Record Groups. (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - National Archives - Index to Letters Received by Confederate AIG and QMG. (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - National Archives - Index to Letters Received by Confederate Secretary of War. (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - National Archives - Pamphlets. (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
  - National Archives - Unfiled Papers and Slips Belonging to Compiled Service Records. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - New Market. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers - Abingdon Virginian. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers - Danville Monitor. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers - Library of Congress. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers - Lynchburg Daily Virginian. (Box 36, Folder 9-10)
  - Newspapers - Daily Republican (Lynchburg). (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers - The New York Times. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers - Pennsylvania Daily Telegraph (Harrisburg). (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers - Philadelphia Inquirer. (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers - Daily Dispatch (Richmond). (Box 36, Folder 15-17)
  - Newspapers - Daily Dispatch (Richmond). (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers - Daily Richmond Examiner. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers - Richmond Enquirer. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers - Richmond Semi-Weekly Examiner. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers - Richmond Whig. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers - Richmond Whig and Public Advertiser. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers - Sentinel (Richmond). (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers - Southern Advocate (Richmond). (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers - Weekly Dispatch (Richmond). (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers - Wilmington (N.C) Daily Journal (Card File). (Box 51, Folder n/a)
  - Newspapers - Winchester Evening Star. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - North Anna. (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Notations Used in Compiling Rosters. (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Official Records Atlas. (Box 37, Folder 13-14)
  - Official Records Supplement. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Paver, John M. - 5th Ohio Volunteer Infantry - Personal Recollections. (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Pay of Confederate Troops. (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Payne's Farm. (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Petersburg - Battles. (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Petersburg - Fort Sedgwick. (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Philpott, Edwin - 57th Virignia Infantry. (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Port Republic. (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Railroads - Confederate. (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Ranson Diary - 21st VIrginia Infantry. (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - "The Record of Virginia Forces" by Meriwether Stuart. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Richmond Battlefields. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Ruffner, Kevin C.. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Salisbury Prison. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Second Manassas. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Sewell Mountain (Tim McKinney). (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Shenandoah Valley Battlefields. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Shiloh. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Spotsylvania Court House. (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
  - Strasburg, VA. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Subsistence. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Tennessee Pension Applications. (Box 38, Folder 13-15)
  - Tennessee State Library. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Top of Allegheny. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Topographical Maps - Virginia. (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Turner, Clark - 57th Virginia Infantry. (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Uniforms. (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Vicksburg. (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Civil War Centennial Map. (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Military Institute (Al Conner). (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Military Institute Belt Buckle. (Box 52, Folder n/a)
  - Walker, Gary C. - "The War in Southwest Virginia, 1861-1865". (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Wilderness. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Winchester. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - WPA Historical Inventory - Library of Virginia. (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Series III. Alexander Welch Reynolds Research Files., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 39-46)
  The research files on Alexander Welch Reynolds include notes, correspondence, copies of records from archival repositories, including the National Archives, Library of Congress, and West Virginia University, House and Senate documents, published sources, and a military service record of Reynolds compiled by Chapla. The information in this series was used by Chapla for articles on Welch which were published by the Greenbrier Historical Society, and in the New Mexico Historical Review and North Carolina Historical Review.
  - Americans in the Egyptian Army by Pierre Crabites. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Southern Historical Society Papers - Reynolds Brigade and Missionary Ridge. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Annals of Athens, Georgia by Augustus Longstreet Hull. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Athens, 1861-1865, As Seen Through Letters in the University of Georgia Libraries. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Biographical Register of the Officers and Graduates of the U.S. Military Academy. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - The Blue and Gray on the Nile by William B. Hesseltine and Hazel C. Wolfe. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Burnside, Ambrose E. - Rhode Island Historical Society. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Calhoun, James S. - Official Correspondence. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - A Carolinian Goes to War: The Civil War Narrative of Arthur Middleton Manigault. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Carriage Terminology: An Historical Dictionary by Don C. Berkebile. (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Charleston Daily Courier. (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Charleston Mercury. (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Chronicle & Sentinel (Augusta, GA). (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Confederate Athens by Kenneth Coleman. (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - A Confederate Soldier in Egypt by W.W. Loring. (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence/Email. (Box 39, Folder 20-23)
  - Daily Dispatch (Richmond, VA). (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Davenport, William - University of Florida. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Estate Papers of Thomas Reeves and Thomas F. Ash. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Florida During the Territorial Days by Sidney Walter Martin. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Forts of the West by Robert W. Frazer. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Gasbari Palace - Alexandria, Egypt. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Greenbrier (WV) Independent. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - "Historical Sketches of the Army of the U.S." - Journal of the Military Service Institution of the U.S.. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - History of the Second Seminole War by John K. Mahon. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Huntington Library. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Jesup, Thomas Sidney - Library of Congress. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Jordan, W.T.. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Kentucky Profiles: Biographical Essays in Honor of Holman Hamilton (James Guthrie). (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Lewisburg, WV. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Library of Congress. (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Library of Congress - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection. (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Library of Congress - Willis H. Claiborne Diary and Reynolds Brigade Letterbook. (Box 40, Folder 17-18)
  - National Archives Information. (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - National Archives - Compiled Service Records of Confederate Soldiers Who Served in Organizations from the State of Tennessee (M268). (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - National Archives - Compiled Service Records of General Officers and Staff. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - National Archives - Department of State - Records of Foreign Service Posts - Cairo, Egypt. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - National Archives - Jefferson Davis Papers (RG94). (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - National Archives - Jefferson Davis Papers (RG107). (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - National Archives - Jefferson Davis Papers (RG217). (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - National Archives - Jefferson Davis Papers (RG692). (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - National Archives - Letters Received by the Adjutant General's Office (M567). (Box 41, Folder 8-10)
  - National Archives - Letters Received by the Adjutant General's Office - Index to Mexican War Period Letters. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - National Archives - Letters Sent by the Quartermaster General (M745). (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - National Archives - Letters Sent to the President by the Secretary of War (M127). (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - National Archives - Office of the Quartermaster General - Consolidated Correspondence File. (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - National Archives - Quartermaster General Consolidated Correspondence File (RG92). (Box 42, Folder 1-6)
  - National Archives - Quartermaster General Consolidated Correspondence File - File of John B. Grayson. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - National Archives - Quartermaster General Consolidated Correspondence File - File of T.S.J.Johnson. (Box 42, Folder 8-11)
  - National Archives - Quartermaster General Consolidated Correspondence File - File of Thomas Swords. (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - National Archives - Quartermaster General Consolidated Correspondence File - Mexican War. (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - National Archives - Quartermaster General Office - Letters Received from the Secretary of War. (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - National Archives - Records of Federal District Courts (RG21). (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - National Archives - Records of the Judge Advocate General (Army) - Court-Martial Case Files (RG153). (Box 43, Folder 2-8)
  - National Archives - Records of the Quartermaster General - Records Relating to Contracts and Proposals - Registers of Contracts. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - National Archives - Records of Regular Officers of the Quartermaster Department. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - National Archives - Records of the Second Comptroller - General Letters Received (RG217, Entry 182). (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - National Archives - Records of the Secretary of War - Applications for Promotion and Commissions (RG107). (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - National Archives - Records of the U.S. House of Representatives (RG233). (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - National Archives - Register of Letters Received by the Adjutant General's Office (M711). (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - National Archives - Register of Letters Received by HQ, 9th Military Department (M1072). (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - National Archives - Register of Letters Received by HQ, 9th Military Department (M1102). (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - National Archives - Returns From Regular Army Infantry Regiments (M665). (Box 44, Folder 6)